Wow, you are much more manageable without that oversized garden tool of yours
哇哦，你沒了那把過大的柴刀更加身嬌腰柔了啊
Oh man, you know, Perry, I really did need this
爽，Perry啊，我還真需要這個消遣
But seriously
不過說真的
How'd you find this place, Red?
你怎麼找到這兒的，紅毛？
Errr
口亨
Huh?
呃？
Whoa!
哇噢！
I see you got some tricks up your sleeve
看來你還會玩些鬼把戲嘛
Let me make this clear
跟你直說吧
We're not through here yet
咱們還沒完呢
Oh, what the..
哎，我去..
Perry, if you and the boys could take care of that
Perry，能帶你的人去搞定那邊麼
Kind of in the middle of something
稍微陷入了點麻煩
What is going on here?!
他喵的怎麼回事！？
Run!
快跑！
Somebody kill her!
來個人幹掉她！
Attach this car and spread the word: we're starting the train
把這車廂接上然後通知大家：發車了
But we're not finished..
但活還沒完..
Do it, or you're finished
聽話，不然你就完了
Ruby!
Ruby！
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
I'm fine, I'm fine, but listen!
沒事，沒事，先聽我說！
Torchwick's got all sorts of weapons and robots down there
Torchwick在這下面藏了各種武器和機器人
What?
吶尼？
Androids, mechs, they're all loaded up on the train cars
機器人啊，機甲啦，全都裝在火車上
Ah, it's ridiculous, these tunnels are sealed, the tracks lead to a dead end
啊，太諧了，隧道是封住的，這是條死路
Get to your places, we are leaving now
各就各位，我們要出發了
Well, it sounds like they're going somewhere
好吧，看樣子他們是要去某處
We need backup
我們需要支援
Let me call Jaune
我來呼叫Jaune
I can't get through!
打不通啊！
So, what do we do?
那現在怎麼辦？
I believe we only have one option
我認為只有一個選擇
We're stopping that train
停下那輛火車
Huh?
咦？
I think they're on th-
我覺得他們上-
Boss! They made it on the train!
老大！他們上火車了！
Then grab some cargo, and get them off the train!
那就隨便抓些貨物把他們趕下去！
Man, animals, every one of them..
我去，一個個真是動物..
Not you though, you are..
當然沒說你，你..
You're great
你萌萌噠
Alright children, we must get to the front and stop this train
好了孩子們，我們必須去車頭停下火車
Uh, professor..
呃，教授..
Doctor..
是博士..
What's that?
那是什麼？
That my dear..
這個嘛..
appears to be a bomb
貌似是個炸彈
We've got baddies
壞蛋來啦
Well, I can't expect them to go..
好吧，我可不指望他們..
easy on us
輕易放過我們
Time to go
該走了
Blake, decouple the caboose , it will kill us all!
Blake，把乘務車分離，不然會害死我們的！
On it!
瞭解！
Huh?
哎？
It decoupled itself
它自己斷開了
What?
神馬？
I guess he really doesn't want us on this train
看來他真的不想讓我們待在車上
That's not good
這可不妙
Uh, neither is this
呃，這邊也一樣
Another bomb?
另一個炸彈？
No, no no
不是吧
They all have bombs!
每節都有炸彈！
This doesn't make sense!
這不科學啊！
Get the humans!
幹掉那些人類！
Oh..dear
天..哪
He's leading Grimms to the city!
他在把戮獸引進城！
What?!
什麼！？
It's the cars!
用的車廂！
They detached and exploded, creating an opening for the Grimm!
分離之後再爆炸，在隧道裡開口子給戮獸！
That's insane!
簡直瘋了！
We have to hurry!
我們得速度了！
You three, go below and try to stop those bombs
你們三個，去下面試著解除炸彈
What about us?
我們呢？
We're going to stop this train
我們來停下這輛火車
Yeah, I know, I said that earlier
是啊我知道，我之前就說了
Up ahead
就在前面
We've got a problem!
我們遇上麻煩了！
Go!
走你！
I guess this is what we trained for
我們的訓練要派上用場了
Here, this should help you
來，這個應該有幫助
You two go on ahead, this one's mine
你們倆先走，這只我要了
You go on ahead
你先走
Got it
收到
Finally, I get to kill a Schnee
我總算能殺一個雪倪家的了
Hello, Kitty Cat, you miss me?
好呀小貓咪，想我麼？
You know we really ought to stop meeting like this
我們真的不能再像這樣幽會了
People are gonna talk
會有緋聞的
Why are we fighting?
為何要互相殘殺？
I saw you at the rally, we're on the same side and you know it
我在集會上看見你了，我們是一邊的啊你懂的
Come here, princess
給我過來，小公主
Hmm, still feisty
唔，還是這麼辣
So, what're we gonna do now?
那麼，現在我們怎麼辦？
Do you really think a little bow on top is gonna make people forget what you were?
你真以為帶上個小小的蝴蝶結就能讓人忘了你的身份？
What you've done?
忘了你的所作所為？
So what's it gonna be, Blake?
所以你怎麼選，Blake？
Ruby! You go on ahead
Ruby！你先走
Uh, but..
呃，但是..
Don't worry Ruby, it's time I teach them a lesson
別擔心，Ruby，該輪到我教訓他們了
Go
去吧
What do we do?
這可怎麼辦？
BRB
BRB
This SUB is presented by Baidu RWBY Bar Creator: sbz_kid
本字幕由百度RWBY吧提供 片源/翻譯/時間軸/特效/後期：sbz_kid